rock.com 2017-01-25

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, billing address, phone number, or credit card information. 

Various third party vendors use cookies to serve targeted ads on sites you visit after visiting Rock.com, including potentially ads from Rock.com. Some of our third party vendors allow you to opt out of receiving such ads. For more information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed. Addtionally, we utilize various services to identify you when you return to the site so that we may customize your on site experience and subsequently continue to market to you when you leave the site with banner ads on other sites and emails based on your activity while on the site.

Further, we have enabled Google Analytics to collect information about the nature of our users experience while visiting Rock.com including but not limited to Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. This will enable us to continually improve the services we provide to our customers. However, to opt out of Google Analytics, visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

• To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

• To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

• To market to you on social media, search engines, and other websites (this allows us to keep you continually informed and updated regarding product opportunities) 

• To send periodic emails 

The email address you enter into our shopping cart may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc. Further, if you enter your email address to receive any discounts or promotions, you will receive occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc. 

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time without notice. We encourage you to revisit the privacy policy page each time you visit for updated information. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [Store@Rock.com](mailto:Store@Rock.com).
